<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Factory Optic Documentation</title>
    <link>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Factory Optic Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:51:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Connections</title>
      <link>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/connections/</guid>
      <description>Connect SYNCRO-LINK  RS232  Connector on SYNCRO-LINK is DTE DE9M, with power on the Ring Indicator (pin 9) Currently supports Cooke /i protocol and Zeiss eXtended data commands   LTC IN (Analog)  BNC Supports SMPTE timecode   SYNC IN (Analog only)  BNC 75Ω impedance input Supports most Bi-level and Tri-Level genlock formats   DC POWER (OPTIONAL)  8-28VDC input @ 4W max   Ethernet/POE  10/100 Mbit Ethernet IEEE 802.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configuration</title>
      <link>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/configuration/</guid>
      <description>On the side of the SYNCRO-LINK is an microSD slot with a factory installed memory card.
The device should contain a card already, but if you need to replace, it should be formatted as FAT32 and can be up to 32GB.
In the SD card is a folder named &amp;lsquo;config&amp;rsquo;. Inside this folder is the config files for the network.
A fresh copy of the SD Card can be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Display</title>
      <link>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/display/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/display/</guid>
      <description>SYNCRO-LINK Display The SYNCRO-LINK has an onboard OLED display that displays useful information.
Page 1  On the top bar  UDP will indicate whenever UDP packets are streaming, usually takes 45-60 seconds afterbootup if the network settings are correct Firmware version is shown on the right   On the left  ip address of SYNCRO-LINK ip address of destination server port on destination server  DHCP will show next to port if network is configured as DHCP   mac address of SYNCRO-LINK   On the right  LTC/Timecode  This should appear and change every frame when timecode is present When timecode is no longer connected, the last timecode received will show LTC is limited to 30 frames max, but when operating in double-rate video formats, such as 47.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Engine</title>
      <link>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/unreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 23:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://factoryoptic.github.io/public/getting-started/unreal/</guid>
      <description>The SYNCRO-LINK MARK-ZERO makes use of the LONET-Unreal-Plugin created by Andy Jaroz of LOLED VIRTUAL
UE4.26 install  Download the 1.50 plugin from LOLED VIRTUAL&amp;rsquo;S Github site: https://loledvirtual.com/documentation/docs/unrealreleases/ Create a directory named &amp;lsquo;plugins&amp;rsquo; in your Unreal project folder, if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t already exist Unzip the file to the plugins directory  Open project in Unreal Engine  When you launch Unreal, open your project Unreal may warn that files are missing, you can select compile from source to generate if needed Unreal will let you know new plugins are available, make sure the LONET plugin is enabled  LiveLink  Open LiveLink  Select &amp;lsquo;+ Source&amp;rsquo;, then LOLED LiveLink, set the port number to the UDP port you configured in dest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
